Shrishti Jain Chartered Accountant

- ♦ Hash Appartment, CG road, 380009 Ahmedabad, India
- ishrishti07@gmail.com
 ishrishti07@gmail.com
- **\$890720746**

Profile

Experienced Senior Accountant successful at cultivating effective working relationships at all levels while driving improvements to budget administration, expense tracking and forecasting of future financial needs. Proven track record of performing work ethically while maintaining integrity of all financial data. Team Leader experienced in directing activities of workgroups. Develops strategies, provides training, sets goals and obtains team feedback. Excellent interpersonal and communication skills. Big picture focus with excellence in communicating goals and vision to succeed. Problem solver, networker and consensus builder.

Education

04/2014 - 07/2018	Chartered Accountants, Institute of Chartered Accountants of India	Ahmedabad, India
04/2014 - 07/2017	B.Com, Mohanlal Sukhadiya University	Aburoad, India

Professional Experience

12/2020 - present

Team Leader/Senior Associate,

KMK Ventures Private Limited

- Prepared and reviewed federal and state income tax returns in accordance with applicable tax laws.
- Prepared internal and regulatory financial reports, balance sheets and income statements- Monthly Bookkeeping for a clientele of 8 companies
- Performed routine closings, maintained clean, accurate and accessible records and kept close eye on transaction updates throughout each quarter.
- Oversaw high-volume accounting operations with two person team focused on efficient budget administration, AP/AR and other financial management needs.
- Handled a team of 12 members
- Generated sales tax reports for each operational jurisdictions, monitored bi-weekly payroll and prepared and paid out sales commissions.
- Built strong relationships with customers through positive attitude and attentive response.
- Initiated timely response to emails, voicemails and written correspondence.
- Prepared cash flow projections, cost analysis and monthly, quarterly and annual reports.
- Reconciled accounts and reviewed expense data, net worth and assets.

Ahmedabad, India

01/2020 - 07/2020 **Associate**, Rhythm Business Advisory Private Limited Ahmedabad, India GST returns • TDS Returns • New GST Applications • Monthly Accounting • Lead a team of 5 people • Income Tax returns for Individuals and partnership firms 02/2019 - 11/2019 Associate, Amit H Gupta & Co. Ahmedabad, • Handled 4 Insolvent companies by myself India • Handled AP and AP • Prepared various reports for the Court which are basic requirements to track the progress of the companies like Preliminary report, Monthly reports, Progress Report. • Handled GST and TDS Return filing Handled Income Tax return filing 11/2020 - 12/2020 **Content Writer**, Youth India Foundation Work from homs, India • Used various software like Canva to stylize the content • Utilized exceptional writing, editing and proofreading skills to produce engaging and error-free content. • Repurposed and optimized existing content for use in different mediums. • Provided writing support in fast-paced environment for variety of public-facing materials. • Wrote and edited high-quality content and visually impactful programs under deadline pressure with exciting, captivating and authentic approach. 09/2020 - 10/2020 **Account Assistant,** Wudstreet Investment Private Limited Work from • Used advanced software like Zoho and Tally to prepare home, India documents, reports and presentations. • Created Excel sheet to mark the investments return on a daily basis. • Attended various Fund managers call to discuss the viability of the fund • Prepared reports and materials to assist with audits. • Tracked funds, prepared deposits and reconciled accounts. • Documented sales, customer interactions and concerns and generated update reports for senior management. · Validated and recorded invoices and resolved discrepancies with vendors. 07/2020 - 2020 Article Trainee, IIFL Limited Work from • Created a clientele of 10 clients to learn stock home, India

• Created financial report for various companies to make

• Initiated comprehensive account assessments to check viability, stability and profitability of business operations.

sure they should be bought or notReported ROIs using Excel spreadsheets.

management

08/2015 - 11/2018

Article Assistant, V CAN & Co

- Ahmedabad, India
- Tax returns of Individuals and listed companies like Hindustan Dorr Oliver Limited and HDO Technologies Limited
- Concurrent Bank audit of Bank of Baroda, State Bank of India, Bank of India
- Statutory audit of Union bank of India
- Internal Finance Control for Lendingkart Technologies and Lendingkart Finance Private Limited
- Service tax returns for 100 clients
- Excise return filings for 20 clients
- VAT Return filings for 40 clients
- Consultation of TDS and GST to Lendingkart Finance and Lendingkart Technologies Pvt limited.
- Rewrote financials for 5 years of various companies to be submitted to SEBI for IPO
- 15CA CB filing

Skills

Accounting	Taxation
Quickbooks	Proconnect
Xero	Lacearte
Tally	Taxslayer
Zoho	Genius

Communication

Team leader

Communication channels

Teams Slack Front

Problem solving

Time tracking softwared

Toggle Clickup

Meeting deadlines

Sales tax returns filing

Languages

English	••••	Hindi	••••
French	• • • • •	Gujarati	• • • • •

Certificates

· Quickbooks Pro advisor

Xero Pro advisor

Interests

Reading, Writing, Learning new things, Walking, Watching series